Finding Aid for the Martin Perlich Interviews PASC-M.0341
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Interviews, Series 1.
  - Jeffreys, Garland, 1978 May 2; audio cassette (Box 10)
  - Jo, Sumi, 2003 July 30; minidisc (Box 4)
    Duration: 32:43
  - Joachim, Marco, 2007 March 8; compact disc (Box 5)
  - Joel, Billy, 1977 October 7; audio cassette (Box 4)
  - Joel, Billy, 1977 October 1; compact disc (Box 7)
  - Johansen, David, audio cassette (Box 11)
  - Johnstone, Jyll, 2008 April 9; compact disc (Box 5)
    On item, "Hats Off."
  - Jones, O-Lan, 2007 November 27; compact disc (Box 9)
  - Kaczmarek, Jan, 2006 January 13; compact disc (Box 5)
    On item, "Arts and Roots Forum."
  - Kaczmarek, Jan, 2006 January 19; compact disc (Box 7)
  - Kaczmarek, Jan, 2006 November 1; compact disc (Box 7)
  - Kahane, Jeffrey, 2001 December 6; minidisc (Box 4)
    Recorded at Zipper Hall.
  - Kahane, Jeffrey, 2001 January 26; minidisc (Box 4)
  - Kahane, Jeffrey, 2002 November 12; DAT (Box 6)
  - Kahane, Jeffrey, compact disc (Box 8)
    On disc, "Segments."
  - Kahane, Jeffrey, 2006 October 10; compact disc (Box 9)
    Duration: 29:10.
  - Kajese, Tinashe, 2008 September 25; compact disc (Box 5)
    On disc, "Victory."
  - Kaplan, Ameenah, 2006 April 5; compact disc (Box 5)
  - Kaskcow, Ruth, 2005 February 18; DAT (Box 8)
  - Kaufman, Annette, 2006 April 11; compact disc (Box 7)
  - Kaufman, Annette, 2007 June 26; compact disc (Box 7)
  - Kaufman, Annette, 2006 May 4; compact disc (Box 9)
    Duration: 30:06
  - Keach, Stacy, 2007 October 10; compact disc (Box 7)
  - Keach, Stacy, 2007 October 15; compact disc (Box 9)
    Duration: 30:01.
  - Kim, Martha, 2008 January 4; compact disc (Box 7)
  - King, Robert, compact disc (Box 8)
  - Kingston, Alex, 2006 December 6; compact disc (Box 5)
    With Brendan Fox.
  - Kirschner, Robert, 2008 February 14; compact disc (Box 5)
    Recorded at the Skirball Museum.
  - Knussen, Oliver, 10" open reel audio tape (Box 1)
  - Knussen, Oliver, 1990; 10" open reel audio tape (Box 2)
  - Kosinski, Jerzy, 1979 September 10; audio cassette (Box 4)
    Recorded at the Beverly Hilton hotel.
    On item, "Passion Play." Compact disc copy in box 9.
  - Koszinski, Jerzy, 1979 September 10; compact disc (Box 7)
  - Kovacevich, Stephen, 2001 April 27; minidisc (Box 4)
    Duration: 40:33
  - Kovacevich, Stephen, 1990; Master. 1 10" audio tape. (Box 2)
  - Kovacevich, Stephen, Master tape. 1 10" audio tape (Box 3)
  - Kovacevich, Stephen, 2001 January 18; DAT (Box 6)
  - Kovacevich, Stephen, 2001 April 27; compact disc (Box 7)
  - Kovacevich, Stephen, 1990 June 29; compact disc (Box 8)
    Disc 2 of 2. Disc 1 missing. Copy on audio cassette in box 11.
  - Kovacevich, Stephen, 1989 July 14; audio cassette (Box 11)
  - Kraft, William, streaming video
  - Kraft, William, 2005 November 14; compact disc (Box 9)
  - Kraft, William, 2003 January 14; minidisc (Box 9)
  - Kraning, Blue, 2007 June 7; compact disc (Box 5)
  - Kronos Quartet: Joan Jeanrenaud, 10" open reel audio tape (Box 2)
  - Kronos Quartet, 10" open reel audio tape (Box 3)
  - Kronos Quartet, 2008 October 3; compact disc (Box 8)
  - Krouse, Ian, 2007 February 8; compact disc (Box 5)
  - Krouse, Ian, 2007 February 1; compact disc (Box 5)
    On disc, "Mid-Summer Night's."
  - Krouse, Ian, 2007 April 30; compact disc (Box 5)
  - Krouse, Ian, 2004 December 8; DAT (Box 8)
  - Labeque, Marielle and Katia, 10" open reel audio tape (Box 2)
  - Laine, Cleo, 10" open reel audio tape (Box 2)
  - Laine, Cleo, 1989 January 18; audio cassette (Box 11)
  - Landler, Edward, 2005 April 19; compact disc (Box 5)
  - Lang Lang, 2002 December 4; minidisc (Box 4)
    Duration: 27:41
  - Lapica, Monty, 2007 August 31; compact disc (Box 5)
  - Lauridsen, Morten, streaming video
  - Lauridsen, Morton, 2005 March 21; compact disc (Box 5)
  - Lauridsen, Morton, 2005 March 24; compact disc (Box 9)
  - Lawrence, Sharon, 2006 January 16; compact disc (Box 5)
  - Layton, Stephen, 2007 February 12; compact disc (Box 7)
  - Lazarof, Henri, 2008 January 24; compact disc (Box 8)
  - LeBaron, Anne, streaming video
  - LeBaron, Anne, 2006 March 30; compact disc (Box 7)
  - LeBaron, Anne, 2005 November 21; compact disc (Box 7)
  - LeBaron, Anne, 2006 March 16; compact disc (Box 7)
  - LeBaron, Anne, 2008 January 16; compact disc (Box 8)
  - LeBaron, Anne, 2007 November 13; compact disc (Box 9)
  - LeBow, Peter, 2006 May 2; compact disc (Box 5)
  - Lefkowitz, David, 2007 February 19; compact disc (Box 7)
  - Legawiec, Stephen, compact disc (Box 5)
    On disc, "Fafalo."
  - Legawiec, Stephen, 2008 April 3; compact disc (Box 7)
  - Leinsdorf, Erich, 10" open reel audio tape (Box 1)
  - Lemieux, Marie-Nicole, 2006 December 13; compact disc (Box 7)
  - Lentz, Daniel, streaming video
  - Lewitzky, Bella, 1990; 10" open reel audio tape (Box 2)
  - Lewitzky, Bella, 1990 June 20; audio cassette (Box 11)
  - Lieberson, Lorraine Hunt, 2005 June 9; compact disc (Box 9)
    Duration: 29:55.
  - Lin, Chio-Liang, 1990 July 31; audio cassette (Box 11)
    Subject is an American violinist
  - Lindberg, Magnus, 2002 April 4; minidisc (Box 4)
  - Livingston, Guy, 2004 January 8; minidisc (Box 4)
  - Livingston, Guy, 2006 January 27; compact disc (Box 9)
  - Lloyd, Suzanne, 2006 September 12; compact disc (Box 5)
  - Loggins, Kenny, 1977 September 8; audio cassette (Box 10)
    Also includes interview of August 20, 1978.
  - Lokumbe, Hannibal, streaming video
  - Lovelace, Paul, 2006 March 23; compact disc (Box 5)
  - Lowe, Nick, 1978 June 5; audio cassette (Box 6)
  - Lubin, Steven, 10" open reel audio tape (Box 2)
  - Lutoslawski, Witold, 1989 August 8; audio cassette (Box 11)
  - Lutoslawski, Witold, 10" open reel audio tape (Box 1)
    Master tape.
  - Luxon, Benjamin, 10" open reel audio tape (Box 2)
  - Luxon, Benjamin, 1990 February 6; audio cassette (Box 6)
  - Lynott, Phil, 1979 June 26; audio cassette (Box 10)
    Of the band, Thin Lizzy.
  - Ma, Yo Yo, 10" open reel audio tape (Box 2)
  - Ma, Yo Yo, 1990 October 19; audio cassette (Box 11)
    Duration: 18:55.
  - MacAdams, Jay, 2008 February 7; compact disc (Box 5)
  - Macdonald, Heather Lyn, 2006 September 28; compact disc (Box 5)
    On disc, "Been Rich All My Life."
  - MacKerras, Sir Charles, 10" open reel audio tape (Box 3)
  - Maddalena, James, 10" open reel audio tape (Box 2)
  - Maddalena, James, 1990 August 23; audio cassette (Box 12)
    On item, "Nixon in China."
  - Mander, Jerry, audio cassette (Box 6)
    On container: "2 of 2."
  - Maria Leon de la Vega, Sonia, 2008 January 31; compact disc (Box 7)
  - Maria Leon de la Vega, Sonia, 2007 November 8; compact disc (Box 7)
  - Maria Leon de la Vega, Sonia, 2008 February 7; compact disc (Box 9)
    Duration: 29:28
  - Maria Leon de la Vega, Sonia, 2007 November 10; compact disc (Box 9)
    Duration: 25:55.
  - Marins, Andre, 2007 October 30; compact disc (Box 5)
  - Marins, Andre, 2007 November 1; compact disc (Box 7)
  - Marsalis, Branford, streaming video
  - Martinez, Ana Maria, 2006 June 20; compact disc (Box 9)
  - Marwood, Anthony, 2006 February 5; compact disc (Box 7)
  - Matalla, Perla, 2007 February 20; compact disc (Box 9)
    Duration: 30:11
  - Mauceri, John, 2002 July 17; minidisc (Box 4)
    Duration: 61:29
  - McCormack, Jessie, 2007 September 19; compact disc (Box 5)
    On disc, "Journey to Dollywood."
  - McDermott, Anne-Marie, 2003 May 8; DAT (Box 8)
  - McFadden-Talbot, Jack, 2006 April 27; compact disc (Box 5)
  - McFadden-Talbot, Jack, 2006 April 19; compact disc (Box 5)
  - McLaughlin, Jon, 1977 October 19; compact disc (Box 7)
    2 discs. Copy on audio cassette in box 11.
  - McNeely, Joel, 2006 April 26; compact disc (Box 5)
  - MDI Ensemble, 2006 November 6; compact disc (Box 7)
    Recorded in Milan, Italy.
  - Means, Russell, 1995 November 30; audio cassette (Box 10)
  - Mednick, Murray, 2005 April 4; compact disc (Box 7)
  - Mednick, Murray, 2003 July 3; DAT (Box 6)
  - Mednick, Murray, compact disc (Box 9)
    Duration: 30:28.
  - Mednick, Murray, 2005 April 7; compact disc (Box 9)
    Duration: 30:18.
  - Mehta, audio cassette (Box 12)
  - Mehta, Zubin, 1988 April 12; audio cassette (Box 12)
    Duration: 35:36
  - Menkes, Nina, 2007 March 14; compact disc (Box 5)
  - Menuhin, Yehudi, 10" open reel audio tape (Box 2)
  - Menuhin, Yehudi
  - Menuhin, Yehudi, 1990 February 10; compact disc (Box 7)
    Duration: 47:04
    2 discs. Audio cassette copy in box 12. Copy on one compact disc in box 9.
  - Menuhin, Yehudi
  - Menzies, Mark, 2006 October 27; compact disc (Box 7)
  - Mester, Jorge, 10" open reel audio tape (Box 1)
  - Mester, Jorge, 2002 October 31; DAT (Box 8)
  - Mester, Jorge, 1990 January 12; audio cassette (Box 12)
  - Metheny, Pat, 1979; 1 12" sound disc (Box 3)
  - Metheny, Pat, 1979 February 20; audio cassette (Box 4)
    master tape. Compact disc copy (2 discs) in box 7.
  - Meyer, Edgar, 2006 April 7; compact disc (Box 8)
    On disc, "Audition Booth."
  - Michetti, Michael, 2008 March 31; compact disc (Box 5)
  - Midnight Special, compact disc (Box 8)
  - Miller, David Allen, 10" open reel audio tape (Box 3)
  - Miller, Jonathan, audio cassette (Box 6)
  - Miller, Jonathan, 1 10" audio tape (Box 1)
    Scope and Content
  - Millikan, Ann, 2007 April 30; compact disc (Box 8)
    On disc, "The Audition Booth."
  - Milnes, Sherrill, 1990; compact disc (Box 8)
    Duration: 68:21
    2 discs. Copy on one compact disc in box 9.
  - Milnes, Sherrill, audio cassette (Box 12)
  - Nathan Milstein Centenary, 2003 December 31; DAT (Box 8)
    Interviews with Bruce Dkov and Clayton Haslop.
  - Mitchell, Rick, 2007 January 4; compact disc (Box 5)
  - Money, Eddie, 1978 April 10; audio cassette (Box 4)
  - Moore, Dudley, 10" open reel audio tape (Box 1)
    With Jonathan Miller
  - Moore, Dudley, audio cassette (Box 6)
  - Moretti, Isabelle, 2004 June 10; DAT (Box 6)
  - Moretti, Isabelle, 2005 June 21; compact disc (Box 9)
    Duration: 30:09
  - Morrison, Bill, 2007 March 5; compact disc (Box 7)
  - Morrison, Bill, 2008 January 7; compact disc (Box 7)
  - Mortier, Gerard, 1990; 10" open reel audio tape (Box 2)
    Recorded in Salzburg.
  - Mortier, Gerard, 1990 June 26; audio cassette (Box 12)
  - Muhl, Erica, 2006 March 20; compact disc (Box 7)
  - Muhl, Erica, 2004 July 28; DAT (Box 8)
  - Muldaur, Maria, 1979 July 10; audio cassette (Box 10)
  - Mull, Martin, 1973 January 6; 10" open reel audio tape (Box 1)
    audio cassette copy in box 10
  - Mull, Martin, 1979 May 4; compact disc (Box 7)
  - Mull, Martin, 1979 May 24; audio cassette (Box 10)
    Duration: 34:55.
  - Mull, Martin, 1977 October 12; audio cassette (Box 11)
    On container, "music only?"
  - Murray, Michael, 2008 May 12; compact disc (Box 5)
    On disc, "Night of the Iguana."
  - Mustonen, Olli, 2003 April 25; minidisc (Box 4)
  - Mustonen, Olli, 2001 March 7; minidisc (Box 4)
  - Mustonen, Ollie, 2001 March 7; compact disc (Box 9)
    Duration: 33:43.
  - Mutter, Anne-Sophie, 10" open reel audio tape (Box 1)
  - Natamatsu, Jon, 2004 August 27; DAT (Box 8)
  - Newman, Mitch, 2007 October 25; compact disc (Box 5)
  - Netrebko, Anna, 2003 December 11; minidisc (Box 4)
  - Newman, Maria, 2006 March 24; compact disc (Box 7)
  - Newman, Maria, 2006 March 31; compact disc (Box 8)
  - Newman, Randy, 1977 September 20; audio cassette (Box 6)
    Recorded in Los Angeles.
    2 audio cassettes. Compact disc copy (3 discs) in box 7.
  - Newman, Randy, 1977 September 20; compact disc (Box 8)
    Disc 2 of 3. Discs 1 and 3 missing.
  - Newmark, Mary Lou, streaming video
  - Newmark, Mary Lou, 2008 May 21; compact disc (Box 5)
  - Nimoy, Leonard, 2002 December 4; DAT (Box 6)
  - O'Connor, Mark, 2003 February 26; minidisc (Box 4)
  - O'Dette, Paul, 2002 February 8; DAT (Box 6)
  - O'Dette, Paul, 2005 May 19; compact disc (Box 7)
  - Ohlssohn, Garrick, 2001 May 2; minidisc (Box 4)
  - Ohlsson, Garrick, compact disc (Box 8)
  - O'Keefe, Danny, 1979 June 6; audio cassette (Box 11)
  - Ophuls, Marcel, 1988 October 11; audio cassette (Box 10)
  - Ophuls, Marcel, 10" audio tape (Box 3)
  - Oppens, Ursula, 1989 May 30; audio cassette (Box 11)
  - Orbison, Roy, 1979 May 8; audio cassette (Box 4)
    Recorded at the Beverly Hills Hotel, Los Angeles.
  - Palmer, Robert, audio cassette (Box 10)
    On item, "pt. 1."
  - Pamela Z, 2006 October 13; compact disc (Box 8)
  - Pearl, Judea, 2007 January 16; compact disc (Box 5)
  - Pearl, Judea, 2007 January 25; compact disc (Box 9)
    Duration: 29:58.
  - Pennington, John, 2006 October 31; compact disc (Box 5)
  - Perlman, Itzhak, 1967; 10" open reel audio tape (Box 3)
  - Peters, Tom, 2007 September 28; compact disc (Box 5)
  - Petrov, Nikolai, 1988 November 30; audio cassette (Box 12)
  - Phelps, Ben, 2007 May 5; compact disc (Box 5)
  - Phoenix, Charles, 2005 June 14; compact disc (Box 5)
  - Pier, Dave, 2005 May 25; compact disc (Box 8)
    With Mark Valdez.
  - Pinnock, Trevor, audio cassette (Box 12)
  - Pitt, Suzan, compact disc (Box 5)
  - Plowright, Jonathan, 2006 October 11; compact disc (Box 5)
  - Plum, Ego, streaming video
  - Podger, Rachel, 2005 March 8; DAT (Box 6)
  - Pollack, Lucy, 2007 January 30; compact disc (Box 5)
    On item, "safety."
  - Pollack, Daniel, 2007 September 28; compact disc (Box 7)
  - Pollack, Daniel, 1990 February 1; audio cassette (Box 11)
  - Pop, Iggy, 1977 August 25; audio cassette (Box 10)
  - Previn, Andre, 10" open reel audio tape (Box 1)
  - Previn, Andre, 10" open reel audio tape (Box 2)
  - Previn, Andre, 10" open reel audio tape (Box 3)
  - Previn, Andre, 1990 April 14; compact disc (Box 7)
    audio cassette copy in box 11.
  - Previn, Andre, 1990 September 21; audio cassette (Box 12)
  - Prine, John, 1978 June 9; audio cassette (Box 4)
    Recorded at the Los Angeles Sunset Marquis.
  - Prine, John, 1978 June 9; audio cassette (Box 6)
    2 cassettes.
  - Proctor, audio cassette (Box 10)
    On container, "Proctor and Bergman."
  - Ptaszynska, Marta, 2005 October 13; compact disc (Box 5)
    With Marek Zembrowski.
  - Poundstone, Paula, 2006 June 7; compact disc (Box 5)
    Subject is a comedian.
  - Pure Prairie League, 1978 May 23; audio cassette (Box 6)
    Subject is an American country rock band
  - Purim, Flora, 1977 October 13; compact disc (Box 7)
    With Airto Moreira.
  - Raffo, Heather, 2005 September 23; compact disc (Box 5)
  - Rattle, Simon, 10" open reel audio tape (Box 1)
  - Ray, Vicki, streaming video
  - Ray, Vicki, 2007 November 6; compact disc (Box 5)
  - Ray, Vicki, 2007 April 24; compact disc (Box 8)
  - Reed, Lou, 10" open reel audio tape (Box 1)
    Electric Tongue broadcast.
  - Reed, Lou, 1979 May 2; audio cassette (Box 10)
    Recorded at Cafe Russe in Beverly Hills, Ca.
  - Reich, Steve, 10" open reel audio tape (Box 1)
  - Reich, Steve, 1989 Decmeber 1; compact disc (Box 8)
  - Reich, Steve, 2004 October 20; minidisc (Box 9)
  - Reich, Steve, 2007 January 25; minidisc (Box 9)
    Also with Grant Gershon.
  - Reich, Steve, 1978 September 5; compact disc (Box 9)
  - Reich, Steve, 2004 October 24; compact disc (Box 9)
  - Reich, Steve, 2008 April 19; compact disc (Box 9)
  - Reich, Steve, 1978 September 25; audio cassette (Box 11)
    2 tapes. master tape. Also on compact disc in box 9.
  - Riddle, Young, 2006 February 7; compact disc (Box 7)
  - Riddle, Young, 2006 April 18; compact disc (Box 7)
  - Rifkin, Joshua, 10" open reel audio tape (Box 2)
  - Rilling, Helmuth, 10" open reel audio tape (Box 2)
  - Rilling, Helmuth, 2004 April 14; minidisc (Box 4)
  - Rilling, Helmuth, 1990 May 2; audio cassette (Box 12)
  - Ritenour, Lee, 1978 August 7; audio cassette (Box 6)
  - Ritenour, Lee, 1979 June 20; audio cassette (Box 6)
  - Ritter, Rosemary Hyler, 2007 June 18; compact disc (Box 5)
  - Roberts, Marcus, 2002 Feburary 14; audio cassette (Box 4)
  - Robertson, Robbie, 1980; audio cassette (Box 4)
    On item, "Carny."
  - Robertson, Robbie, 1978 January 5; compact disc (Box 7)
    2 discs. Master tape on 2 audio cassettes in box 11.
  - Robertson, Robbie, 1980 April 21; audio cassette (Box 10)
  - Robinson, Michael, 2007 April 2; compact disc (Box 5)
  - Robson, Mark, 2006 February 8; compact disc (Box 5)
  - Rodriguez-Elliot, Julia, 2007 November 26; compact disc (Box 5)
  - Rodgriguez-Elliott, Julia, 2007 November 29; compact disc (Box 7)
  - Rogerson, Hank, 2006 May 10; compact disc (Box 5)
    On disc, "Shakespeare Behind Bars."
  - Rogerson, Hank, 2006 May 25; compact disc (Box 5)
  - Rohde, Kurt, streaming video
  - Rolie, Greg, audio cassette (Box 11)
    Of the group, Journey.
  - Romero Family, 10" open reel audio tape (Box 1)
  - Ron, Yuval, 2006 October 25; compact disc (Box 7)
  - Ron, Yuval, 2004 February; DAT (Box 8)
  - Rosen, Charles, streaming video
  - Rubinstein, John, 2008 March 4; compact disc (Box 5)
    Duration: 30:02
  - Rudel, Julius, 2003 November 11; minidisc (Box 4)
  - Russell, Craig, 2005 July 21; compact disc (Box 7)
  - Rysanek, Leonie, 10" open reel audio tape (Box 3)
  - Sachs, Steven, 2008 January 25; compact disc (Box 5)
    Duration: 29:08.
    On disc, "Victory." Compact disc copy in box 9 also includes Tinashe Kajese.
  - Sadeghi, Manoocher, 2007 May 20; compact disc (Box 9)
    Duration: 29:21.
  - Salerno-Sonnenberg, Nadia, 2007 April 11; compact disc (Box 7)
  - Salerno-Sonnenberg, Nadia, 2007 August 9; compact disc (Box 9)
  - Salonen, Esa-Pekka, 2001 January 9; compact disc (Box 8)
    master recording. Minidisc copy in box 9.
  - Salonen, Esa-Pekka, minidisc (Box 9)
  - Salonen, Esa-Pekka, 2002 January 10; minidisc (Box 9)
  - Salonen, Esa-Pekka, audio cassette (Box 11)
    Includes a report by Alan Rich.
  - Sandoval, Gema, 2007 October 19; compact disc (Box 5)
  - Savall, Jordi, 2001 February 23; minidisc (Box 4)
  - Savedoff, Allen, 2005 February 14; DAT (Box 8)
  - Sayer, Leo, 1978 July 7; audio cassette (Box 11)
  - Schickel, Erika, 2007 January 8; compact disc (Box 5)
  - Schickele, Peter, 2007 June 4; compact disc (Box 7)
  - Schickele, Peter, minidisc (Box 9)
  - Schickele, Peter, 2007 June 7; compact disc (Box 9)
  - Schifrin, Lalo, streaming video
  - Schirle, Joan, 2008 February 7; compact disc (Box 5)
  - Schneider, John, 2007 May 2; compact disc (Box 7)
  - Schneider, John, 2008 April 10; compact disc (Box 7)
  - Schneider, John, 2006 October 26; compact disc (Box 7)
  - Schrader, Barry, streaming video
  - Schrader, Barry, 2005 September 22; compact disc (Box 7)
  - Schrader, Barry, 2006 February 13; compact disc (Box 7)
  - Schrader, Barry, 2006 May 30; compact disc (Box 7)
  - Schroeder, Pierre, 2008 March 26; compact disc (Box 5)
  - Schwarz, Gerard, 1990 August 24; audio cassette (Box 12)
  - Scorsese, Martin, 1978 January 6; audio cassette (Box 4)
    Recorded in Los Angeles. Duration: 31:19
    master tape. Copy on compact disc in box 9.
  - Scott, John, 2006 May 5; compact disc (Box 5)
  - Scott, Patrick, 2005 April 27; compact disc (Box 5)
    On disc, "Mladi."
  - Scott, Patrick, 2006 February 6; compact disc (Box 5)
  - Scott, Patrick, 2000 April 20; compact disc (Box 5)
    On disc, "Jacaranda."
  - Scott, Patrick, 2007 November 5; compact disc (Box 5)
  - Scott, Patrick, 2007 November 8; compact disc (Box 7)
  - Sefton, David, 2006 January 18; compact disc (Box 5)
  - Sellars, Peter, 2004 October 21; DAT (Box 8)
  - Sellars, Peter, 2005 April 18; compact disc (Box 9)
  - Sellars, Peter, 1990 August 22; audio cassette (Box 11)
  - Sellars, Peter, 10" open reel audio tape (Box 1)
  - Sendak, Maurice, 10" open reel audio tape (Box 2)
    Subject is a writer.
  - Sendak, Maurice, 1990 September 12; audio cassette (Box 10)
  - Serebrier, Jose, 2005 Feburary 19; DAT (Box 6)
  - Serebrier, Jose, 2008 February 7; compact disc (Box 7)
  - Serebrier, Jose, 2005 July 7; compact disc (Box 9)
    Duration: 29:20. Also with Carole Farley.
  - Serebrier, Jose, 2004 December 20; compact disc (Box 9)
    Duration: 29:15. Also with Carole Farley.
  - Severinsen, Doc, 1990 August 10; audio cassette (Box 10)
  - Shaham, Gil, 2004 April 22; minidisc (Box 4)
  - Shankar, Ravi, 10" open reel audio tape (Box 2)
  - Shankar, Ravi, 1988 December 2; 12" LP sound disc (Box 3)
    Features music from Shankar's new album,"Inside the Kremlin."
    Audio casset in box 10.
    Digital transfer in DLP
  - Shankar, Ravi, 1987 May 26; audio cassette (Box 4)
  - Shankar, Ravi, 1989 March 17; audio cassette (Box 12)
  - Shiffrin, David, 10" open reel audio tape (Box 1)
    Digital copy in DLP
  - Shostakovich, Maxim, 2002 October 27; minidisc (Box 4)
  - Showing Our Age, 2008 April 8; compact disc (Box 5)
    Includes interviews with Laurel Ollstein, Robert Anderson and Melody Butiu.
  - Simon, Richard, 2008 June 5; compact disc (Box 5)
  - Skinner, E. Benjamin, 2008 April 17; compact disc (Box 5)
    On disc, "slavery."
  - Slatkin, Leonard, 10" open reel audio tape (Box 1)
  - Smith, Kurtwood, 2007 April 4; compact disc (Box 5)
  - Smith, Wadada Leo, streaming video
  - Snow, Phoebe, 1977 November 16; audio cassette (Box 10)
  - So Percussion, 2007 September 24; compact disc (Box 7)
  - Southwest Chamber Music, streaming video
  - Spano, Robert, 2004 May 13; minidisc (Box 4)
  - Spence, Adrian, 2007 November 13; compact disc (Box 5)
  - Spivakov, Vladimir, 1990 August 8; audio cassette (Box 11)
  - Starker, Janos, 10" open reel audio tape (Box 3)
  - Starker, Janos, 1988 November 22; audio cassette (Box 12)
  - Steinberg, Russell, 2007 October 25; compact disc (Box 5)
  - Steinmetz, John, 2003 April 29; DAT (Box 6)
  - Stemple, James, 2006 May 25; compact disc (Box 5)
  - Stern, audio cassette (Box 6)
    Isaac Stern?
  - Stern, Isaac, 10" open reel audio tape (Box 3)
  - Stern, Isaac, 1989; compact disc (Box 7)
  - Stern, Isaac, 1989; compact disc (Box 7)
  - Stern, Isaac, audio cassette (Box 11)
  - Steven T., 1977 October 31; audio cassette (Box 4)
    Recorded in Los Angeles
  - Stills, Stephen, 1979 June 13; audio cassette (Box 4)
    Recorded on Stone Canyon Road, Bel Air. On container, "Cuba al Fin." master tape
  - Stills, Stephen, 1979 June 13; compact disc (Box 7)
  - Stucky, Sephan, 10" open reel audio tape (Box 1)
  - Subotnick, Morton, 10" open reel audio tape (Box 2)
  - Subotnick, Morton, 1990 June 4; audio cassette (Box 12)
    Also on CD in box 9.
  - Swed, Mark, streaming video
  - Swiller, Josh, 2007 October 1; compact disc (Box 5)
  - Szell, George, 1965; 10" open reel audio tape (Box 3)
  - Taj Mahal, 1971 August; 10" open reel audio tape (Box 2)
  - Taj Mahal, audio cassette (Box 6)
  - Taj Mahal, 1998 March 22; audio cassette (Box 6)
  - Taj Mahal, audio cassette (Box 10)
  - Tannenbaum, Robert, 2007 February 1; compact disc (Box 5)
    Recorded at UCLA.
  - Tannenbaum, Robert, 2007 February 8; compact disc (Box 5)
  - Tate, Jeffrey, Master tape. 1 10" audio tape. (Box 3)
  - Taub, Robert, 10" open reel audio tape (Box 2)
  - Te Kanawa, Kiri, 10" open reel audio tape (Box 3)
  - Tedesco, Denny, 2008 June 24; compact disc (Box 5)
  - Tedesco, Penny, 2008 June 26; compact disc (Box 5)
  - Temianka, Henri, 10" open reel audio tape (Box 1)
  - Thibaudet, Jean Yves, 2001 January 18; minidisc (Box 4)
  - Thibaudet, Jean-Yves, 2001 November 22; DAT (Box 8)
  - Thibaudet, Jean Yves, 1990 September 11; audio cassette (Box 12)
  - Thoms, Tracie, 2008 June 5; compact disc (Box 5)
  - Thoms, Tracie, 2008 June 3; compact disc (Box 5)
  - Tower, Joan, minidisc (Box 9)
    Subject is an American composer.
  - Traister, Andrew, 2007 October 15; compact disc (Box 5)
  - Trio Voronezh, 2006 September 15; compact disc (Box 5)
  - Trio Voronezh, 2006 October 26; compact disc (Box 5)
  - Tsing-Loh, Sandra, 2005 March 10; compact disc (Box 7)
    Subject is an actor
  - Tuckwell, Barry, 10" open reel audio tape (Box 1)
    Subject is a horn player
  - Uchida, Mitsuko, minidisc (Box 4)
    Subject is a pianist
  - Uchida, Mitsuko, 2001 January 18; DAT (Box 6)